works we need them because they're
there I'm not going to berate and and go
on to this hopefully you can
see what sort of weird narrative I'm
trying to bring up where someone builds
trust okay I'm simply trying to
understand that it it's like no matter
no matter who you're talking to I'm not
talking about the brightest most you
know sharp people that you're trying to
talk I'm talking when I'm talking to my
average American
people these are the dictating thoughts
these are the the over story these are
the terrifying tenants which lock
people into a belief the the conviction
people
the not knowing that you're being
invariable when you are not kn knowing
that you're being too adaptive when you
are the Fool's game everyone it's April
1st it's it's a new time a new place
it's not New Year's anymore we've grown
uh and we've recognized that the way
that we communicate is not attractive
the way that we want to bring up the
fact that fools love fools the fact that
I'm a fool and I Fall For Fools but I
see the pain of the Fool's game and and